{
    "id":"MA_Pub_07",
    "TotalLevel": 5,
    "GameType" : "CompareGame",
    "IntroText": {
        "Type": "PlainText",
        "Content": "請比較兩邊的定位版中的數字大小，並拖曳>、<或=到框框中"
    },
    "GameConfig": {
        "CustomeSymbol": true,
        "SystemSymbol": "BigSmall",
        "WithImage": false,
        "CheckAnswerMode": "Button"
    },
    "Questions": [
        [
            {
                "QuestionText": "數字比大小",
                "Description": "把>、<或=拖曳到框框中",
                "SlotComponentVerifycation": false,
                "Datas": [
                    [
                        {
                            "Name" : "NumberBoard",
                            "Data": {
                            "Unit": ["千位", "百位", "十位", "個位"],
                            "Number": 990
                            }          
                        },
                        {
                            "Name" : "NumberBoard",
                            "Data": {
                            "Unit": ["千位", "百位", "十位", "個位"],
                            "Number": 1000
                            }                 
                        }
                    ]
                ],
                "Answer": ["Small"]
            },
            {
                "QuestionText": "數字比大小",
                "Description": "把>、<或=拖曳到框框中",
                "SlotComponentVerifycation": false,
                "Datas": [
                    [
                        {
                            "Name" : "NumberBoard",
                            "Data": {
                            "Unit": ["千位", "百位", "十位", "個位"],
                            "Number": 5311
                            }               
                        },
                        {
                            "Name" : "NumberBoard",
                            "Data": {
                            "Unit": ["千位", "百位", "十位", "個位"],
                            "Number": 6311
                            }              
                        }
                    ]
                ],
                "Answer": ["Small"]
            },
            {
                "QuestionText": "數字比大小",
                "Description": "把>、<或=拖曳到框框中",
                "SlotComponentVerifycation": false,
                "Datas": [
                    [
                        {
                            "Name" : "NumberBoard",
                            "Data": {
                            "Unit": ["千位", "百位", "十位", "個位"],
                            "Number": 8712
                            }              
                        },
                        {
                            "Name" : "NumberBoard",
                            "Data": {
                            "Unit": ["千位", "百位", "十位", "個位"],
                            "Number": 8439
                            }              
                        }
                    ]
                ],
                "Answer": ["Big"]
            }
        ],
        [
            {
                "QuestionText": "數字比大小",
                "Description": "把>、<或=拖曳到框框中",
                "SlotComponentVerifycation": false,
                "OptionBarTitle": "把>、<或=拖曳到框框中",
                "Datas": [
                    [
                        {
                            "Name" : "NumberBoard",
                            "Data": {
                            "Unit": ["千位", "百位", "十位", "個位"],
                            "Number": 2135
                            }             
                        },
                        {
                            "Name" : "NumberBoard",
                            "Data": {
                            "Unit": ["千位", "百位", "十位", "個位"],
                            "Number": 2132
                            }            
                        }
                    ]
                ],
                "Answer": ["Big"]
            },
            {
                "QuestionText": "數字比大小",
                "Description": "數字比大小",
                "SlotComponentVerifycation": false,
                "Datas": [
                    [
                        {
                            "Name" : "NumberBoard",
                            "Data": {
                            "Unit": ["千位", "百位", "十位", "個位"],
                            "Number": 9874
                            }             
                        },
                        {
                            "Name" : "NumberBoard",
                            "Data": {
                            "Unit": ["千位", "百位", "十位", "個位"],
                            "Number": 9894
                            }           
                        }
                    ]
                ],
                "Answer": ["Small"]
            },
            {
                "QuestionText": "數字比大小",
                "Description": "把>、<或=拖曳到框框中",
                "SlotComponentVerifycation": false,
                "Datas": [
                    [
                        {
                            "Name" : "NumberBoard",
                            "Data": {
                            "Unit": ["千位", "百位", "十位", "個位"],
                            "Number": 3560
                            }             
                        },
                        {
                            "Name" : "NumberBoard",
                            "Data": {
                            "Unit": ["千位", "百位", "十位", "個位"],
                            "Number": 3952
                            }             
                        }
                    ]
                ],
                "Answer": ["Small"]
            }
        ],
        [
            {
                "QuestionText": "數字比大小",
                "Description": "把>、<或=拖曳到框框中",
                "SlotComponentVerifycation": false,
                "Datas": [
                    [
                        {
                            "Name" : "NumberBoard",
                            "Data": {
                            "Unit": ["千位", "百位", "十位", "個位"],
                            "Number": 3418
                            }             
                        },
                        {
                            "Name" : "NumberBoard",
                            "Data": {
                            "Unit": ["千位", "百位", "十位", "個位"],
                            "Number": 2981
                            }            
                        }
                    ]
                ],
                "Answer": ["Big"]
            },
            {
                "QuestionText": "數字比大小",
                "Description": "把>、<或=拖曳到框框中",
                "SlotComponentVerifycation": false,
                "Datas": [
                    [
                        {
                            "Name" : "NumberBoard",
                            "Data": {
                            "Unit": ["千位", "百位", "十位", "個位"],
                            "Number": 6000
                            }              
                        },
                        {
                            "Name" : "NumberBoard",
                            "Data": {
                            "Unit": ["千位", "百位", "十位", "個位"],
                            "Number": 6001
                            }             
                        }
                    ]
                ],
                "Answer": ["Small"]
            },
            {
                "QuestionText": "數字比大小",
                "Description": "把>、<或=拖曳到框框中",
                "SlotComponentVerifycation": false,
                "Datas": [
                    [
                        {
                           "Name" : "NumberBoard",
                            "Data": {
                            "Unit": ["千位", "百位", "十位", "個位"],
                            "Number": 4672
                            }             
                        },
                        {
                            "Name" : "NumberBoard",
                            "Data": {
                            "Unit": ["千位", "百位", "十位", "個位"],
                            "Number": 4672
                            }            
                        }
                    ]
                ],
                "Answer": ["Equal"]
            }
        ],
        [
            {
                "QuestionText": "數字比大小",
                "Description": "把>、<或=拖曳到框框中",
                "SlotComponentVerifycation": false,
                "Datas": [
                    [
                        {
                            "Name" : "NumberBoard",
                            "Data": {
                            "Unit": ["千位", "百位", "十位", "個位"],
                            "Number": 6232
                            }             
                        },
                        {
                            "Name" : "NumberBoard",
                            "Data": {
                            "Unit": ["千位", "百位", "十位", "個位"],
                            "Number": 6270
                            }              
                        }
                    ]
                ],
                "Answer": ["Small"]
            },
            {
                "QuestionText": "數字比大小",
                "Description": "把>、<或=拖曳到框框中",
                "SlotComponentVerifycation": false,
                "Datas": [
                    [
                        {
                            "Name" : "NumberBoard",
                            "Data": {
                            "Unit": ["千位", "百位", "十位", "個位"],
                            "Number": 4001
                            }              
                        },
                        {
                            "Name" : "NumberBoard",
                            "Data": {
                            "Unit": ["千位", "百位", "十位", "個位"],
                            "Number": 3999
                            }             
                        }
                    ]
                ],
                "Answer": ["Big"]
            },
            {
                "QuestionText": "數字比大小",
                "Description": "把>、<或=拖曳到框框中",
                "SlotComponentVerifycation": false,
                "Datas": [
                    [
                        {
                            "Name" : "NumberBoard",
                            "Data": {
                            "Unit": ["千位", "百位", "十位", "個位"],
                            "Number": 4950
                            }              
                        },
                        {
                            "Name" : "NumberBoard",
                            "Data": {
                            "Unit": ["千位", "百位", "十位", "個位"],
                            "Number": 4590
                            }             
                        }
                    ]
                ],
                "Answer": ["Big"]
            }
        ],
        [
            {
                "QuestionText": "數字比大小",
                "Description": "把>、<或=拖曳到框框中",
                "SlotComponentVerifycation": false,
                "Datas": [
                    [
                        {
                            "Name" : "NumberBoard",
                            "Data": {
                            "Unit": ["千位", "百位", "十位", "個位"],
                            "Number": 7089
                            }             
                        },
                        {
                            "Name" : "NumberBoard",
                            "Data": {
                            "Unit": ["千位", "百位", "十位", "個位"],
                            "Number": 7708
                            }              
                        }
                    ]
                ],
                "Answer": ["Small"]
            },
            {
                "QuestionText": "數字比大小",
                "Description": "把>、<或=拖曳到框框中",
                "SlotComponentVerifycation": false,
                "Datas": [
                    [
                        {
                            "Name" : "NumberBoard",
                            "Data": {
                            "Unit": ["千位", "百位", "十位", "個位"],
                            "Number": 1034
                            }              
                        },
                        {
                            "Name" : "NumberBoard",
                            "Data": {
                            "Unit": ["千位", "百位", "十位", "個位"],
                            "Number": 1304
                            }             
                        }
                    ]
                ],
                "Answer": ["Small"]
            },
            {
                "QuestionText": "數字比大小",
                "Description": "把>、<或=拖曳到框框中",
                "SlotComponentVerifycation": false,
                "Datas": [
                    [
                        {
                            "Name" : "NumberBoard",
                            "Data": {
                            "Unit": ["千位", "百位", "十位", "個位"],
                            "Number": 1350
                            }             
                        },
                        {
                            "Name" : "NumberBoard",
                            "Data": {
                            "Unit": ["千位", "百位", "十位", "個位"],
                            "Number": 1035
                            }             
                        }
                    ]
                ],
                "Answer": ["Big"]
            }
        ]
    ]
}